Guide to the Stanford University, Libraries, Diversity Committee, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Libraries, Diversity Committee, records
1989-1996
SC0837
Stanford University. Libraries. Diversity Committee.
2 Linear feet
Collection includes agenda, minutes, memos, reports, correspondence, photographs, and other records.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Collection includes agenda, minutes, memos, reports, correspondence, photographs, and other records.
Access Terms
Long, Linda; Stanford University. Libraries. Diversity Committee.; Diversity in the workplace.; Multiculturalism
Collection Contents
- Records
  - Memos and Minutes 1991-92 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Memos, Etc. 1990-93 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - All-Staff Memos and Articles 1989-91 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - UCMI Report and Related 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - University-Produced Minority/Diversity Issues Documents 1989-93 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - University-Produced Reports on Minority/Diversity Issues 1990-91 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 0
  - Photographs 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Affirmative Action Steering Committee I 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Affirmative Action Steering Committee II 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Affirmative Action Steering Committee III 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Amity Program 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Contact Lists for Exempt and Non-Exempt 1990-93 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Contact Lists 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cultural Outreach Librarian 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Disabilities Workshop 1990-91 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Guideline for Hiring Supervisors 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Meeting Minutes and Agenda 1990-93 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Memos and Minutes 1992-94 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Memos 1990-93 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Emails and Calendars I 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Emails and Calendars II 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Internship Program 1991-96 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Diversity Committee Agenda 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Diversity Committee Meeting Minutes 1995-96 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Funding 1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Staff Composition Analyses 1995-96 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Diversity Committee Report for M. Keller 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - “Minutes” from Binder 1992-94 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - “Agenda” from Binder 1992-93 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - “Ethnic Composition” from Binder 1992-93 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - “Disability Workshop” from Binder 1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - “Notes from Meetings” from Binder 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - “Miscellaneous” from Binder 1992-93 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - “Mission Statement” from Binder 1992-93 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - “Gay and Lesbian Program” from Binder 1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)